accessmba.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy

We understand the importance of privacy to the users of the Websites. When using personally identifiable information Advent Group strictly complies with the applicable data privacy legislation and is committed to observing strict data privacy standards and safeguarding your privacy online. The data controller with respect to the Websites is ATENDIA Ltd., a limited liability company incorporated under Bulgarian law including its subsidiaries and affiliates (together referred to as “Advent Group”, “we” or “us”), registered with the Bulgarian Commercial Register under no. 200967502, with a seat and business address at 20 Serdika Str, Sofia 1000, Bulgaria.

We collect and processes your personal data to facilitate your use of the Websites and their full functionalities, as well as to provide you the Services. In particular, we collect your personal data such as but not only full name, address, email address, telephone number, education, pace of work, professional experience, education- and/or job- related preferences. You voluntarily register on the Websites, thus providing us with your personal data, to avail yourself of the full functionalities of the Websites and to be provided with Services, the provision of which requires prior registration. If you do not wish to provide us your personal data, don’t register on the Websites and don’t use the Websites.

We may provide your personal data only to trusted partners, for the purpose of facilitating your use of the Website and/or for provision of the Services. Some of our partners are located on the territory of the EU/EEU, thus, we may transfer your personal data to countries from the EU/EEA. If a partner is located outside of the territory of the EU/EEA, we may transfer your data also to such third countries, subject to compliance with all applicable data protection rules.

We may also use your data for direct marketing purposes on our behalf or on behalf of any of our partners. By registering on the Websites, you agree among others to the use of your personal data for direct marketing purposes. If at any point of time, including when registering on the Websites you disagree with the use of your personal data direct marketing purposes, please send an email to [webmaster@accessmba.com](mailto:webmaster@accessmba.com) or click the “Unsubscribe” button at the bottom of the message you have received from us.

In accordance with the applicable data privacy legislation, you have the right to access to your personal data and to request its correction.

For any queries you may have on our processing of your personal data, please contact [webmaster@accessmba.com](mailto:webmaster@accessmba.com). 

Cookies are small files a website or its service provider transfers to your device through your web browser that enables the website or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information on your internet uses, preferences, etc.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your device warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our Services may not function properly. 

You can control and/or delete cookies as per your preferences - for details, see [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).
